<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogspotter</title>
    <description>A collection of conversations with the style influencers of the web.</description>
    <link>https://blogspotter.co/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://blogspotter.co/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 15:07:52 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 15:07:52 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Fashion Law</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you’re curious about what’s happening in the legal world of fashion, &lt;strong&gt;The Fashion Law&lt;/strong&gt; by &lt;strong&gt;Julie Zerbo&lt;/strong&gt; is the place to be. Julie started writing articles in law school as a way to learn more about fashion law - and just a short time later &lt;strong&gt;The Fashion Law&lt;/strong&gt; was born. Today, TFL is frequented by both lawyers and non-lawyers who are looking for their daily-dose of fashionable legal commentary. We’re hooked, and if you’re not already - you should be, too. Meet &lt;strong&gt;Julie Zerbo&lt;/strong&gt; of &lt;strong&gt;The Fashion Law&lt;/strong&gt; with Blogspotter today.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’re obsessed with The Fashion Law. Tell us about what made you want to launch TFL.&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you. I only decided to launch the website as an afterthought. At the end of my first year of law school, one of my professors mentioned fashion law to me, and I was immediately intrigued by the marriage between the two fields, fashion and law. So, I started researching and writing on my own, exploring core legal concepts in the context of the fashion industry, as a way to learn about the topic. After a while, I had quite an archive of articles and decided to start sharing them in the form of a blog, because there really were not many sites at the time that were consistently providing content on fashion law and the business of fashion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When did you officially start blogging?&lt;/strong&gt; It feels like a very long time ago. I launched the site in 2012.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’re a lawyer - a profession far different from almost anything in fashion as many of us know it. Did you study fashion as an undergrad before heading to law school? If not, how did you fall into fashion?&lt;/strong&gt; I did not. My prior studies were in economics and international business. At that point in time, I was editing an economics journal and very much planning to pursue a career in that field. However, I took an internship with a law firm in my final semester of college (after taking a rudimentary business law course) and when it came time to graduate, my parents, who are both extremely smart, suggested law school, and I thought, “Sure, why not?” And so I went. My initial intention was to focus on constitutional law, though. I never pictured myself working in fashion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My interest in fashion is twofold, really. I have always had a significant appreciation for well-made, well-designed garments, and upon learning a bit about the core concepts of law, I was intrigued by the integral role that they play in the business of fashion. There is a lot more to fashion than meets the eye, and this is what drives me now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s your main source of content inspiration? Do you frequent any websites, blogs, or publications to get information, or does press contact you directly?&lt;/strong&gt; I frequent a lot of rather nerdy websites, such as Westlaw and Pacer (two big legal databases). I get most of my inspiration in terms of pending cases from these sites. As for the more general fashion-oriented articles on my site, overarching trends and issues in the industry often inspire me, such as why has London been such a hot bed for young talent over the past decade or what is the core objective of designer collaborations beyond the surface goal of selling the specific collection, these come from just being in the industry, I suppose, and being inquisitive beyond the most obvious trends, such as red for Fall/Winter 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t really read other blogs too much because I get frustrated, as I tend to think everything should be academic or cerebral, or have substantial context, when that certainly is not the case. As for websites, I read Business of Fashion very regularly. I read absolutely everything that Vanessa Friedman of the New York Times writes. She is so sharp. Alexander Fury of The Independent is up there, as well. John Koblin, who writes for the New York Times, has also been on my radar lately. I also love that Cathy Horyn is back and writing for NY Magazine’s site! (I know I am forgetting someone here!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My one personal style blog exception is BryanBoy, who I admire because he doesn’t promote fast fashion and actually purchases a lot of his own clothing, which I think is refreshing and authentic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fashion law encompasses a variety of subjects, including copyright, trademark, and licensing (to name a few). What is your favorite thing to blog about/report on - and how do you typically get started? How long does an article take to complete - from start to finish?&lt;/strong&gt; My favorite thing to write about is probably the trends in law or business in connection with the fashion industry. Much like the way fashion is representative of the time in which we are living, the trends in legal cases or ways of doing business are very much like this, as well. I also really enjoy writing about individuals in the industry who I admire. Raf Simons is a very good example of this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t say that I have a set way of doing things. I am very lucky because I have the freedom to write about whatever I think is important at any given time and can approach the writing process in varying ways. Honestly, a lot of my writing begins on my iPhone in the car or during fashion month, for instance, I was doing a lot while I was waiting for shows to start. However, because there is a lot of research that goes into most of the posts, there is obviously a lot of time sitting in front of the computer, as well. As for time, some posts are very time-consuming, taking me an hour here, an hour there over a few days. Other posts, such as purely news ones, take 15 minutes at most.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How would you describe your personal style?&lt;/strong&gt; Black. I almost always wear black and I’m not terribly girly. So, dark jeans and a Jil Sander tee or Prada knit tank top is usually it for me. I’m also very, very minimalist in terms of silhouettes and accessories. I hate jewelry (with the exception of a red bracelet that I never take off) and I hate the idea of dressing for attention. So, I suppose my personal style is best characterized as straightforward with an emphasis on the quality of my wardrobe. I have always preferred one really nice garment to five trendy, lower quality ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tell us what you’re wearing to the courtroom (to defend your client, of course).&lt;/strong&gt; In terms of work, I try to dress rather conservatively. I can’t stand skirt suits or the other stereotypical female lawyer staples, but a black blouse and trousers with a classic Manolo heel feels safe to me. That’s not to say I don’t wear cropped Haider pants or a Chalayan top from time to time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QUICK! Prada or Gucci?&lt;/strong&gt; Prada!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QUICK! Forever21 or H&amp;amp;M?&lt;/strong&gt; Prada!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you blog full-time? If not, how do you balance your full-time job with the demands of a heavily referenced resource blog?&lt;/strong&gt; I do not. I have never actually blogged full time. I have always either been in school full time or working. I guess I have just chosen from early on to prioritize the website and as a result, I make time for it. So, you very rarely will see me at fashion parties! I’m at home writing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are there any websites or online resources that you turn to for guidance with respect to blogging and maintaining your blog?&lt;/strong&gt; Not that I can think of. From the beginning, the blogging process has been very trial and error and I have learned a lot this way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Does social media play a big part in your blogging process? Do you have any general “rules of thumb” that you abide by when posting to social media?&lt;/strong&gt; Social media is more of a secondary tool, a way for me to connect with readers and people who value the same things I do, such as high fashion (as opposed to fast fashion), education, and things like that. I don’t really have any rules of thumb. My social media presence isn’t terribly calculated like that and I think that’s what people generally respond to – that sense of authenticity. I did rather recently, however, launch my own personal Twitter to try to separate the personal from the TFL brand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are your thoughts on branded email marketing/campaigns - do you find that they help you build your brand’s viewership base?&lt;/strong&gt; I don’t do anything like that. I don’t think I have ever really participated in things that actively seek to build a readership. I probably should, but that’s just not really what I’m about. I would much rather spend my time writing and researching, and I think it is important to just let my work speak for itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s the most rewarding component of blogging?&lt;/strong&gt; The relationships I’ve built. I met my mentor, Barbara Kolsun, as a result of my website. That has to be one of the single most rewarding results thus far. She has been practicing in this sector for so many years and is has such a wealth of valuable knowledge about law and the business of fashion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, being able to speak to an audience and share knowledge is pretty powerful, in my opinion. I gain a lot of joy from being able to emphasize the importance of education and intelligence to my peers and those that are even younger than me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s one thing that blogging has taught you that you never expected to learn?&lt;/strong&gt; It has taught (and continues to teach) me to be true to my vision, and to be objective at all costs, which is much more difficult than it sounds!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2015 09:00:35 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://blogspotter.co/the-fashion-law/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blogspotter.co/the-fashion-law/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Interviews</category>
        
        <category>Lifestyle</category>
        
        <category>t</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Black Barcode</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Black Barcode&lt;/strong&gt; is what &lt;strong&gt;Madeline Smith&lt;/strong&gt; defines as a “place to come if you need help picking an outfit out for the next day”. She blogs to provide creative dressing inspiration for her readers, while giving them a sneak peek into her life. We love the glitter and gold scattered about &lt;strong&gt;The Black Barcode&lt;/strong&gt; and adore Madeline’s passion for her work. Meet &lt;strong&gt;Madeline&lt;/strong&gt; of &lt;strong&gt;The Black Barcode&lt;/strong&gt; with Blogspotter today.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tell us about The Black Barcode.&lt;/strong&gt; The Black Barcode is a place to come if you need help picking an outfit out for the next day. It’s to help inspire others to want to get dressed and be creative with what they are wearing. Not only will you find fashion inspiration but also to see the places I’ve been and food I’ve had and things I’ve purchased. It’s an inside look into my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How did you choose the name and color scheme for your blog?&lt;/strong&gt; The name for my blog came from a project I did in 11th grade photograph. It was just showing how everyone dresses the way they are told from media, and not having a personal style. Everyone in my school wore leggings, Uggs and Northface jackets; they wore the same thing everyday. So the name “The Black Barcode” is basically a spin from that, barcodes all look the same, and I wanted my blog to show you that you don’t have to fit in with what you are told. I choose the color scheme for my blog because you can never go wrong with a little gold and glitter!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where do you find blogging inspiration?&lt;/strong&gt; I find inspiration from other bloggers. I follow a ton of bloggers and check their sites everyday to get inspiration on what is on trend, or ways to style different things. I feel like if they can do it, I can do it, so it inspires me to keep going!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Give us a brief description of your personal style.&lt;/strong&gt; My personal style is pretty classic; I wear a lot of red white and blue, and try to be as put together as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QUICK! Heels or flats?&lt;/strong&gt; Flats for now! I’m in school and it’s just much easier to go class to class in my favorite Tory Burch Reva flats!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QUICK! Gelato or ice cream?&lt;/strong&gt; Ice Cream! I love making my own at home by adding in caramel sauce or mini M&amp;amp;M’s!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you take more cues from street style or runway fashion?&lt;/strong&gt; I get more from runway fashion because I can take what’s on the runway and make outfits from current pieces I already own for a much affordable price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How much time do you typically allot to complete a blog post? (From start to finish, including “thinking”, photography, editing, and content writing)&lt;/strong&gt; It usually depends on what I’m doing, sometimes I can figure out what I want to post quickly, but others take time, I post every other day so I’ll give myself that time to do everything!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you could only wear one outfit everyday for the rest of your life, what would it be?&lt;/strong&gt; Well it would have to include a J.Crew excursion vest, because I own about 6 of them. I would wear a classic outfit, my Steve Madden riding boots, probably my J.Crew herringbone vest, a soft black long sleeve shirt with dark wash jeans. For jewelry my monogram necklace, gold watch and Kate Spade bow ring!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What has social media done for your blog? What platform has had the biggest impact on your audience growth?&lt;/strong&gt; I’m currently only on Instagram (@monobelleprep) and Pinterest (theblackbarcode) and Twitter (@theblackbarcode). I started off on Instagram before ever starting a blog, so Instagram probably has helped connect my follows to my blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who takes your photographs for you? What camera do you use?&lt;/strong&gt; Really anyone that is around that day, so usually my best friend, boyfriend, or sister! I have a Canon T3I and absolutely love it! I wish I were able to take my own photos since I love photography just as much!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s the coolest thing that’s happened since you started blogging?&lt;/strong&gt; Becoming friends with a lot of other fashion bloggers, and making great connections with people I wouldn’t have without my blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you could have done anything differently since you began blogging: what would it be, and why?&lt;/strong&gt; Take photos in different locations. I can still do that, but I wish I had used a variety of different locations in my earlier posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What has starting and maintaining a blog taught you?&lt;/strong&gt; To be organized, and how to plan. It takes a lot of time to come up with the finish product, so being organized can save you a lot of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Any advice for aspiring bloggers?&lt;/strong&gt; Be yourself and use original content.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2015 09:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://blogspotter.co/the-black-barcode/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blogspotter.co/the-black-barcode/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Fashion</category>
        
        <category>Interviews</category>
        
        <category>t</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UF Fashion Files</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Michelle Champalanne&lt;/strong&gt; launched &lt;strong&gt;UF Fashion Files&lt;/strong&gt; in 2012 as a class assignment. Now, she continues to blog and post part-time (she’s still in school) about everything from personal style to do-it-yourself tutorials. She confesses that the key to taking an amazing photo is “just to practice”, admits she’d opt for pink/rose gold over yellow gold any day, and stresses how important a media kit is for any blog. Meet &lt;strong&gt;Michelle&lt;/strong&gt; of &lt;strong&gt;UF Fashion Files&lt;/strong&gt; with Blogspotter today.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How long ago did you start UF Fashion Files?&lt;/strong&gt; I started UF Fashion Files in fall 2012 as a class assignment, but later fell in love with blogging and continued to post for the next 3 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When you started your blog, what did you have in mind? Has it stayed pretty true to that original idea?&lt;/strong&gt; Originally, I wanted to feature only University of Florida students and their fashionable outfits. But, when my course load piled up and my free time on campus vanished, I started to tweak my site to have more fashion tips as well as outfit ideas. During the summer months, I photographed looks I wore back home and featured them on my blog. Now, my blog is more personal with outfit ideas, inspiration posts and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you blog full-time, or is it just a hobby right now?&lt;/strong&gt; Blogging is definitely a hobby for me, since I’m still in school right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We all know the saying: a photo speaks a thousand words. What’s the key to taking a good photo?&lt;/strong&gt; When I take photos, or have photos taken, I always make sure there’s a ton of options. I’ve learned over time what are the most flattering angles and how to operate my DSLR to get high-quality images. The key is just to practice!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How has blogging gone for you so far? Do you feel it was a worthwhile endeavor?&lt;/strong&gt; I love blogging. It can get tough at times when I feel overwhelmed with school and my internship. But, when I have free time, I love putting up a new post and connecting with my readers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Give us a brief description of your personal style.&lt;/strong&gt; I would say that my style is classic and comfortable. I grew up in California, so I definitely embodied that Southern California laid-back style when it comes to getting dressed. I always reach for comfy soft shirts and flowy dresses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where do you see yourself in 5 years?&lt;/strong&gt; In five years, I see myself working at a fashion or women’s magazine as a contributing writer. I would also hope to freelance for other publications on the side, as well as still write for my blog!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QUICK! Pink gold or yellow gold?&lt;/strong&gt; Pink gold! I have two rose gold diamond rings and a rose gold dainty heart necklace that I wear every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you could only wear one outfit everyday for the rest of your life, what would it be?&lt;/strong&gt; That’s a hard choice. My outfit changes on my mood, as cliche as that sounds! But my go-to look is always a chambray shirt with jeans and ballet flats. You can’t ever go wrong and you’re always comfortable! I love fun accessories, so with a look like this, I’ll wear bright shoes or a cool bag and my favorite pair of sunglasses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What has social media done for your blog? What platform has had the biggest impact on your audience growth?&lt;/strong&gt; Social media is one of my favorite parts of blogging. I love Instagram; it’s always awesome getting inspiration from designers and other bloggers, as well as meeting other college fashion bloggers. It’s such a great way to not only spread your blog’s influence, but make new friends, too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s one thing that blogging has taught you that you did not expect to learn?&lt;/strong&gt; How important a media kit can be. I made one for my site over the summer and I didn’t realize how fun it would be to put together! It has helped a lot with collaborations and building business connections. I love working with design so I’m hoping one day I can redesign my blog myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you could start your blogging journey all over, would you change anything?&lt;/strong&gt; There are a few minor things I would have tweaked but for the most part, I love my blog. It’s definitely been a learning experience, but a fun one! I never blog when I can’t put my 110% of effort into it because I want my readers to really enjoy what I post. The one thing I would change would be my name, since I am graduating in May. But, that’s easily changeable and I may already have something coming up in the future (wink, wink).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What quote or mantra do you live by?&lt;/strong&gt; I don’t know who said it but I love the quote “Don’t be like the rest of them, darling.” I painted it on a canvas for my freshman year of college as a little daily reminder to stay true to myself. It’s still one of my favorites!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Any advice or personal anecdotes for aspiring bloggers?&lt;/strong&gt; Just have fun. So many more people are blogging now, so it’s important to just be unique and continue to post as long as you’re enjoying it. Blogs are supposed to be fun not only for your readers, but for you, as well. So don’t be afraid to try something new and write about it; you’re making memories that you’ll never forget.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 09:00:55 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://blogspotter.co/uf-fashion-files/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blogspotter.co/uf-fashion-files/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Fashion</category>
        
        <category>Interviews</category>
        
        <category>u</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Primp &amp; Proper</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We’re totally into Kristyn Royster of Primp &amp;amp; Proper. It’s something about her style, or maybe her glittery southern charm, but we’re sure you’ll feel the same way. Originally from Tennessee but currently residing in Washington, D.C., Kristyn blogs about fashion, style, and more, collaborating with awesome brands like H&amp;amp;M; and Julep. The bubbly blonde gave us a sneak peek into her blogging world. Meet &lt;strong&gt;Kristyn&lt;/strong&gt; with Blogspotter today!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How long have you been blogging for Primp &amp;amp; Proper and what made you start?&lt;/strong&gt; I’ve been blogging for 13+ months now. I originally started blogging back in January 2014 as a way to document my adventures in DC… a.k.a. provide an outlet for my family to keep up with what I’ve been doing, ha! After I got more and more into the blogging scene of DC, I decided to commit fully and grow my blog way beyond an online journal of my time in DC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We love all the gold and glitter in your branding. How did you decide on a name, color scheme and graphics for your blog?&lt;/strong&gt; Thanks! When it came to the design and layout, I wanted to keep it simple and clean. I didn’t want just a black and white theme, so I added a pop of glitter and gold to make the design more fun. I worked with a great designer, Tammy of A Loyal Love, and together we created my site. As for the name, Primp &amp;amp; Proper is a play on a Southern saying, prim and proper. I thought the name fit me and what I was blogging about very well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you balance a full-time job and part-time blogging? Any rules of time management that you live by?&lt;/strong&gt; Well it definitely isn’t easy, ha! I pretty much consider blogging a second full-time job. I spend about 17+ hours a week on blogging and everything that goes into it. For me, it’s all about managing your time and doing what’s necessary first. Instead of trying to do 10 things at once, I categorize my to-do list in order of importance. That way I never miss a deadline. I also use the Day Designer planner, which I highly recommend, that helps me keep track of my day-to-day and daily tasks. I also color code the important tasks and highlight items once they’re finished. I’m OCD about leaving items unchecked or not highlighted, so it helps motivate me to finish what’s on my list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Which item(s) in your wardrobe could you never live without? It really depends on the season.&lt;/strong&gt; For now, it’s definitely my H&amp;amp;M tote. I own it in three colors… yes, three. I love it. Molly Sims even complimented me on it and couldn’t believe it wasn’t a designer handbag. I can’t recommend this tote enough. It’s perfect for work or daily use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aside from your own blog (we hope you are your biggest fan!), do you have a favorite blog?&lt;/strong&gt; It’s so hard to choose just one, but I would say some of the blogs I read daily are Waiting on Martha, Glitter Guide (online magazine), Fashionable Hostess, What Courtney Wore and Sequins &amp;amp; Stripes. I also follow a lot of DC blogs (some of them are even very good friends)! Too many to name, but love them all!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fashion Week is live and happening! Are you super excited about any designers in particular?&lt;/strong&gt; I will admit that this year was the first year I actually sat down and watched some of the shows live. Every year I have to rely on recaps and reviews, simply because Fashion Week is always during busy season at work. This year I watched Tadashi Shoji, Rebecca Minkoff and a few others. I actually did a recap of some of my fave shows here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QUICK: Red matte lips or nude shiny gloss?&lt;/strong&gt; Easy. Nude shiny gloss. I’m all about the subtle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are your must-have items?&lt;/strong&gt; A good tote bag for work, a great pair of heels for work and boots for every day use, a nude gloss and my hot rollers (these are the exact ones I use).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What camera do you use?&lt;/strong&gt; Any tips for taking that perfect photo? I use a Canon SLR. Definitely pay attention to your white balance and ISO (thanks Julien for the tips!!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How long does it typically take to complete a blog post?&lt;/strong&gt; It usually depends on the type of post. One of my more simple posts, like Thursday’s 10 Thoughts, takes about an hour from beginning to end. That includes creating the post, editing photos, proofreading, and then scheduling social media posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A more in depth post, like an outfit of the day or recipe, can take anywhere from 3-4 hours total.&lt;/strong&gt; That includes taking the outfit photos or cooking the recipe. I usually have one of these types of posts max each week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How has social media impacted your blog’s audience?&lt;/strong&gt; Social media is HUGE! It’s super important to share your post and interact with your followers/readers. That only helps to grow your social media following, and ultimately your blog readership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QUICK: Facebook or Instagram?&lt;/strong&gt; Instagram… definitely, Instagram.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s one thing that blogging has taught you that you did not expect to learn?&lt;/strong&gt; That’s a tough one, because I’ve learned SO many things over the past year. I’m still learning new things each and every day. I guess one “surprise” that has come from blogging that I never expected, was how many real life friends I would make through it. Blogging is about sharing your life on the web. I never thought those friends I connected with via Twitter or Facebook, would turn out to be good friends I hang out with all the time. It has been a very nice surprise!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If your sister was about to launch a fashion/style blog tomorrow, what’s one piece of advice you would give her?&lt;/strong&gt; Oh gosh… I feel like I could talk about this question for hours. Simply because I knew nothing when I started my blog. Knew absolutely nothing. I’ve written a few posts about this and have a few more on the way, but my number one piece of advice is to educate yourself on what all goes into having a blog and on protecting yourself. Your blog is a business, so it’s vital you know what all comes along with that.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 09:00:53 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://blogspotter.co/primp-and-proper/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blogspotter.co/primp-and-proper/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Interviews</category>
        
        <category>Lifestyle</category>
        
        <category>p</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Natalia Bosch</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Her self-titled blog is “like a photo diary, a place where I share my personal style, my love for fashion, adventures and basically everything that comes to my mind”. &lt;strong&gt;Natalia Bosch&lt;/strong&gt; of &lt;strong&gt;Natalia Bosch&lt;/strong&gt; has been blogging for just about 4 years. Her self-described personal style is “very eclectic, feminine and diverse”, she adores Chanel, and opts for Instagram over any other social media platform. We’re into her - and think you should be too. Meet Natalia of Natalia Bosch with Blogspotter today.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tell us about your self-titled blog, Natalia Bosch.&lt;/strong&gt; My blog is like a photo diary, a place where I share my personal style, my love for fashion, adventures and basically everything that comes to my mind. I started blogging at a very young age, as I got older my love for fashion grew with me. It wasn’t until I was at my first year of college that I decided to do personal style and outfit’s posts. I was a very insecure girl and the blog somehow helped me to be more confident and embrace who I was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How long have you been blogging for?&lt;/strong&gt; I’ve being blogging for four years. I started my blog in 2011, when I was sixteen years old.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How did you know it was the right time to launch your blog?&lt;/strong&gt; I didn’t. I knew I wanted to have my little corner of inspiration on the web, but I wasn’t sure when was the right time. One thing I’m sure, what motivated me from the beginning to make a blog was the opportunity to share my inspirations and passions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where do you find blogging inspiration?&lt;/strong&gt; I find lots of inspiration in magazines and of course, Instagram.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How would you describe your personal style?&lt;/strong&gt; My personal style is very eclectic, feminine and diverse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you have a favorite brand?&lt;/strong&gt; I have a few favorite brands, but a girl must love Chanel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QUICK! Chocolate chip cookies or sugar cookies?&lt;/strong&gt; Chocolate chip cookies. No doubt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How much time do you typically allot to complete a blog post? (From start to finish, including “thinking”, photography, editing, and content writing)&lt;/strong&gt; It depends, sometimes I schedule certain days to take the photos other times is spontaneous; but, I always make sure the location is the appropriated for the outfit. Outfits photos take from 30 minutes to a 1-hour depending on the climate, lighting, the place, etc. What really consumes my time is choosing the pictures, editing them, putting together the full post with links and written material. That takes me a 1-hour or more. It all depends on the type of post I’m writing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How has social media helped the growth of your blog?&lt;/strong&gt; Social media has helped me expand my blog readers. I reach more people through my posts and it helps me engage more with my followers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you feel that blogging has been a worthwhile endeavor so far?&lt;/strong&gt; Definitely, being a blogger has opened many doors for me, opportunities that I never imagined possible. I feel very lucky that my blog, which started as a hobby is now my job. I wouldn’t change it for anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who takes your photographs for you? What camera do you use?&lt;/strong&gt; Most of the time, my Mom takes my pictures, she has become quite the expert, and my closes friends help me too. I use my Cannon Rebel 5ti with a 75-300mm lens, depending on the photo, we change the lenses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What has starting and maintaining a blog taught you?&lt;/strong&gt; I’ve learned that building a successful blog takes time and dedication. You really need to engage and be passionate about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QUICK! Rounded toe or pointed toe heels?&lt;/strong&gt; For sure, pointed toe heels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you could have done anything differently since you began blogging: what would it be, and why?&lt;/strong&gt; I wouldn’t change anything; I have learned and grow so much from this experience and I’m very grateful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Any advice for aspiring bloggers?&lt;/strong&gt; If you have a passion for something, go for it. Be always yourself and enjoy it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 09:00:51 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://blogspotter.co/natalia-bosch/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blogspotter.co/natalia-bosch/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Fashion</category>
        
        <category>Interviews</category>
        
        <category>n</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BEING/BE</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BreAnne Elenburg&lt;/strong&gt; is the Texan beauty behind &lt;strong&gt;BEING/BE&lt;/strong&gt;. She’s rather new to the blogging world (she officially started blogging August 2014) but she’s getting the hang of it rather quickly: she’s already amassed loyal a following and learned a thing or two. Meet &lt;strong&gt;BreAnne&lt;/strong&gt; of &lt;strong&gt;BEING/BE&lt;/strong&gt; with Blogspotter today.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tell us a little bit about BEING/BE.&lt;/strong&gt; I started my blog to showcase my passion for fashion. The greatest way I know to express myself is through fashion and the more I learn about the industry the more I evolve; my personality, my mood, and sometimes a coffee and/or wine spill is evident through my outfit. After countless hours of following amazing fashion bloggers I decided to start my own to share my creativity in hopes that people will see that style, just like the little ole word “be”, is limitless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’re so curious: how did you come up with the name “BEING/BE”?&lt;/strong&gt; If you were to look up the word “be” in the dictionary, the definition would bore you with the simplicity and vagueness of it. But then again how do you sum up the magnitude of the word? In my opinion, BE is to exist, it’s to take place, to happen or occur, it means to continue or remain as before; BE is whatever you want it to be. That is where the name of the blog came from. I live by a mantra of always being who you are. Well, I’m Being/BE-BreAnne Elenburg.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When did you officially start blogging?&lt;/strong&gt; End of August 2014&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You blog about style and beauty. What’s your favorite thing to blog about?&lt;/strong&gt; Definitely style; beauty is a blast, don’t get me wrong, but fashion is always changing and I love the opportunity my followers give me to keep them up to date with the latest trends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did you formally study fashion as an undergrad? If not, do you find that you’re able to incorporate what you did study into your blog?&lt;/strong&gt; Yes! I was extremely fortunate to study Fashion Merchandising at Texas Christian University.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QUICK! Hot pink or bright yellow?&lt;/strong&gt; Hot pink all the way!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s your favorite brand?&lt;/strong&gt; Oh wow, this a toughie! It’s hard to say what my favorite brand is because they all have unique qualities about them that I like to add to my wardrobe. BUT- I will say you can normally find me in at least one item from J.Crew or Madewell. However, if we are talking designers, I would definitely have to say YSL!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How would you describe your personal style?&lt;/strong&gt; As I mentioned a bit in why I started my blog, defining my personal style would be impossible. I dress how I feel that particular day and this can range from an all-black ensemble for a simple trip to the grocery store to ripped jeans with a flannel and converse for a night out with my girls. You just simply never know!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QUICK! What’s your favorite guilty pleasure food?&lt;/strong&gt; Popcorn! I could eat popcorn for every meal! Add extra butter and nacho cheese seasoning salt and you have heaven in a bucket!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you have a favorite outfit in your wardrobe? What is it?&lt;/strong&gt; My go-to outfit when I’m having just “one of those days” is my most comfortable pair of jeans, a simple top and some type of jacket (usually I go with leather to spice up my life a bit). This outfit is then paired with either flats or pumps, but don’t even try to ask what my favorite pair of shoes is because that is an impossible question!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let’s talk Texas! What’s your favorite thing about Texas, and the south?&lt;/strong&gt;
I love the southern hospitality of living in Texas. Everyone is friendly and I love meeting someone only to feel like I’ve known them my whole life after just five minutes of talking! I also can’t go without mentioning teased hair. Big hair is such a Texas thing and I’m obsessed with it! The bigger the hair the closer to Heaven!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are there any websites or online resources that you turn to for guidance with respect to blogging and maintaining your blog?&lt;/strong&gt; There are a number of successful bloggers that I keep up with on a daily basis. These women are incredibly inspirational to me and I love how each blog is unique in its own way. I also try to stay on top of major retailers and designers to see up and coming trends. And of course, Pinterest; what girl doesn’t love Pinterest?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who takes your photos for you?&lt;/strong&gt; Amanda Marie Lackey is my amazing photographer!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What has starting and maintaining a blog taught you?&lt;/strong&gt; Creating a blog has definitely had its ups and downs. It’s not as easy as it looks! Developing your own unique way that is consistent requires you to look into yourself and figure out the way you want to be perceived. I’ve learned that patience is key and I won’t have a billion dedicated followers overnight, as well. Overall, I’m incredibly grateful for the experience I’ve had because it has taught me to be comfortable in my own skin. There is no right or wrong way to be a blogger except to just be myself and enjoy what I do!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s the most rewarding component of blogging?&lt;/strong&gt; The ability to express myself is definitely the most rewarding component of blogging. There is a much deeper level of satisfaction when you can share your passion with the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Any advice for aspiring bloggers?&lt;/strong&gt; Be YOU! You can try your best to mimic other bloggers but at the end of the day you want to be yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2015 09:00:42 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://blogspotter.co/beingbe/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blogspotter.co/beingbe/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Fashion</category>
        
        <category>Interviews</category>
        
        <category>b</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Peaches In A Pod</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whitney Damrau&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Blaire Bingham&lt;/strong&gt; are the brains behind &lt;strong&gt;Peaches In A Pod&lt;/strong&gt;, a Georgia-based fashion and style blog. They love peach cobbler (yum!), are close family friends (they’ve known each other for over 15 years), and are very thankful for what Instagram has done for their blog and their following. Meet Whitney and Blaire of Peaches In A Pod with Blogspotter today!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**How did you meet? **
Whitney grew up with Blaire’s husband and both families have been friends for many years. When Blaire started dating her husband we were always together.&lt;br /&gt;
It’s crazy that we have known each other for more than 15 years!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**How long ago did you start Peaches In A Pod? **
Peaches In A Pod was started in January of 2014, so we are wee babes in the blog world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**The name (Peaches In A Pod) is so cute! How did you come up with it? **
We have always shared a similar style, and we are always talking fashion, so we are definitely two peas in a pod in that aspect.  We also knew that we wanted to incorporate the fact that we are from Georgia, so put those two together, and Peaches In A Pod was born.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When you started Peaches In A Pod, what did you have in mind? Has it stayed pretty true to that original idea?&lt;/strong&gt;
We have always inspired each other when it comes to fashion, so we started this blog as a way to inspire other women, like us. We have definitely stuck to that ideal, and we hope to continue to inspire with our own fashion experiments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your photos are so beautiful! Who takes your photos for you?&lt;/strong&gt;
Well thank you! We take our own pictures. We make it really fun by leaving the kids and husbands at home and go on outfit shoots. We change in the car in remote locations. Changing into skinny jeans behind a steering wheel gets us into fits of hysterics, and by the end there are hangers, shoes and accessories everywhere!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**How does living in Georgia influence your style? **
The weather in Georgia is constantly changing. It could be in the 40’s in the morning and above 70 by the afternoon, so we incorporate a lot of layers into our style.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you balance family/work/life with blogging?&lt;/strong&gt;
We are still working on that! Thank goodness there are two of us!
&lt;strong&gt;B:&lt;/strong&gt; I work during the day when my kids are at school.
&lt;strong&gt;W:&lt;/strong&gt; I stay at home with my 2 year old and work from home, so juggling that plus the blog has it challenges. It’s amazing how much I can accomplish during nap time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aside from your own blog (we hope you are your biggest fan!), do you have a favorite blog? **
**B:&lt;/strong&gt; My blog inspiration is Sequins and Things. I just love her style!  **W: **I’m loving Southern Curls and Pearls. Caitlin is fabulous and her style is so well put together!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where do you see yourself (with Peaches In A Pod) in a year?&lt;/strong&gt;
That’s a great question! We are planning on making the blog bigger and better by improving the site itself. We want to improve speed and functionality. Hopefully switching blog platforms will allow us to do that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**QUICK: Peach cobbler or peach lemonade? **
**B: **Cobbler definitely!
**W: **OMG both are in my top 5 favorite things! Cobbler!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**If you could only wear one outfit every day for the rest of your life, what would it be? **
**B: **Skinny jeans with a great jacket and statement booties.
**W: **A fit and flare dress, cropped jacket and booties or wedges depending on the season. I am totally a dress girl!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**What camera do you use? **
Canon DSLR.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How long, from start to finish, does it take to complete a blog post? **
**From idea to publication, it takes about a week.  We have several drafts in the works at all times.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**How has social media impacted your blog’s audience? Do you have a favorite platform? **Social media has helped us grow our audience tremendously!  Instagram is probably our favorite, but we also love interacting with brands on Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s one thing that blogging has taught you that you did not expect to learn?&lt;/strong&gt;
We didn’t expect to make the friendships that we have made. We love getting to meet and interact with other bloggers. You would think as a blogger, that you sit in an office all day on a computer, but we are constantly in contact with other bloggers, and it has really been refreshing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What main message would you like to convey to your readers?&lt;/strong&gt;
When we started this blog, we had no idea what we were doing, or if we would have any readers. We are so grateful for each and every viewer, and we are blessed to get to do what we love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Any advice or personal anecdotes for aspiring bloggers?&lt;/strong&gt;
Building a blog community has been the most helpful in getting our blog going.  Joining surrounding blog societies and reaching out to other bloggers has not only built up an audience, but also made this process a lot of fun.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2015 09:00:25 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://blogspotter.co/peaches-in-a-pod/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blogspotter.co/peaches-in-a-pod/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Fashion</category>
        
        <category>Interviews</category>
        
        <category>p</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Miss Erin Says</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Her blog is her creative outlet, with a pinch of sass and a few parts sparkle. &lt;strong&gt;Erin Acheampong&lt;/strong&gt; of &lt;strong&gt;Miss Erin Says&lt;/strong&gt; has a personality as excitable as her blog! She describes her style as classic and feminine with a twist, opts for stripes over polka dots, and loves social media. The coolest thing that’s happened to her? She met the fabulous Tory Burch. Get to know Erin of Miss Erin Says with Blogspotter today.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We love your blog! Tell us a little bit about it.&lt;/strong&gt; My blog is a creative outlet for everything I have to say in a visual and text based format. I highlight fashion and sprinkle in a few savvy beauty tips and a dash of sassy lifestyle events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When did you officially start blogging, and what was it that made you want to start?&lt;/strong&gt; I officially started blogging in November of 2013 like many, current, and future bloggers I had always wanted to start a blog. What inspired me to pursue blogging was the realization that I had become a blogger without a blog! I had been dabbling in guest posting for other blogs and finally the light went off that I could actually do this. I then created Miss Erin Says as a creative space to share my passions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You blog about fashion, beauty, and lifestyle - what’s your favorite thing to blog about, and why?&lt;/strong&gt; My favorite thing to blog about would be fashion and my personal style. When I started my blog I didn’t want to limit myself so I incorporated multiple categories. Over time my favorite highlights have been fashion focused. I think this is due to my true appreciation for clothing as most of my life I didn’t fit into “traditional” sizes. After a weight loss journey I now am on a fashion journey and I love sharing and inspiring others along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where do you find blogging inspiration?&lt;/strong&gt; My blogging inspiration is found within other like-minded women. Diane Von Furstenberg’s quote sums it up best. “The success of every single woman is an inspiration for another.” — D.V.F&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How would you describe your personal style?&lt;/strong&gt; I would describe my personal style as classic and feminine with a twist. I love structured garments and classic iconic shapes. Statement pieces with unique details are what draw me. I believe in wardrobe focal points often found in the form of a great handbag! My go to wardrobe piece is a dramatic skirt thus the twist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QUICK! Polka dots or stripes?&lt;/strong&gt; STRIPES!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QUICK! Lipstick or lipgloss?&lt;/strong&gt; Matte Lipstick&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How has blogging gone for you so far? Do you feel it was a worthwhile endeavor?&lt;/strong&gt; Blogging has been a journey and a getaway into a world that I love. I would say that it has definitely been a worthwhile endeavor. As I have met so many inspirational people. I have learned a ton about myself thus far and learned to challenge myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who takes your photos for you, and what type of camera do you use?&lt;/strong&gt; My best friend turned photographer William (a.k.a. Billy) takes my photos. We currently shoot with a Nikon D5300 but we started with an iPhone5 and well now we are here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s your take on social media? How has social media generally helped with the branding of your blog?&lt;/strong&gt; My take on social media is that is is an amazingly powerful tool that is ever evolving and changing. In terms of branding social media has been a great tool to assist my brand in reaching new audience worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the coolest thing that’s happened since you started?&lt;/strong&gt; That would have to be having the honor of meeting Tory Burch. She was a joy and is one of the most humble, genuine and talented individuals I have ever had the pleasure of meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What has maintaining a blog taught you so far?&lt;/strong&gt; Maintaining a blog has taught me about flexibility. I naturally have a type “A” personality so this has been a challenge for me but I am now learning the fine art of flexibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s one thing that blogging has taught you?&lt;/strong&gt; Blogging has taught me to step outside comfort zone in multiple arenas including social scenarios and within my personal style&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If your best friend decided to launch her own blog, what piece of advice would you give her?&lt;/strong&gt; My advice would be to define three things your voice, who you want to inspire, and why you want to blog. Once you have defined these three aspects REMEMBER them and utilize them throughout your journey as your guides. Then make a plan A and after you have devised plan A be ready for that plan to change. Because, after all, there are 26 letters in the alphabet.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 13:30:15 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://blogspotter.co/miss-erin-says/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blogspotter.co/miss-erin-says/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Fashion</category>
        
        <category>Interviews</category>
        
        <category>m</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Couture Crush</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;She may only be 18 years of age, but &lt;strong&gt;Rei Fujita&lt;/strong&gt; of &lt;strong&gt;Couture Crush&lt;/strong&gt; has the blogging skill of a seasoned pro. The Japanese native bounces back and forth from Tokyo to Hawaii (yes, we’re jealous) and is heavily inspired by both cultures. She cites Blair Waldorf as one of her major sources of style inspiration, adores Audrey Hepburn’s elegance, and swears by IFB (&lt;a href=&quot;http://heartifb.com/&quot;&gt;Independent Fashion Bloggers&lt;/a&gt;) as a must-use tool for newbie bloggers. Meet Ms. Fujita with Blogspotter today.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tell us a little bit about  your blog, Couture Crush.&lt;/strong&gt; My blog is a personal style blog that combines trends and influences from both western and asian culture. My main focus is fashion but I also do beauty trends, DIYs, and travel posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When did you officially start blogging?&lt;/strong&gt; I officially started blogging the Summer of 2013&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’re so jealous you live in Hawaii! How does living in Hawaii influence your style?&lt;/strong&gt; Living in Hawaii, the fashion community here is small, with the style being very casual and laid back, making it hard for me to dress up often. I always have a much more simple style while in Hawaii compared to when I’m back in Japan. It’s really cool to see the contrast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did you formally study fashion as an undergrad? If not, do you find that you’re able to incorporate what you did study into your blog?&lt;/strong&gt; I’m still in high school, so no I have not had any study experience in regards to fashion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s your main source of style inspiration?&lt;/strong&gt; I’m obsessed with Blair Waldorf’s style from Gossip Girl. She has been my biggest style inspiration. Her and Japanese fashion magazines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How would you describe your personal style?&lt;/strong&gt; A mix of preppy, feminine, and classic style.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QUICK! Bikini or monokini?&lt;/strong&gt; Bikini ! I’ve never tried a monokini… yet!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you have a favorite accessory? What is it?&lt;/strong&gt; Handbags are my favorite accessory. I feel like you’re set for anything if you invest in one good handbag. It’s something you will use everyday and if you get a classic style, it’s timeless so you don’t have to worry about switching up handbags. It’ll always be in style!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What about a favorite beauty product?&lt;/strong&gt; Right now my favorite beauty product is Benefit’s They’re Real Push up liner! It makes it so so easy to make a perfect cat eye or clean line! Who ever invented it is a genius.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You mention that you’re inspired by Audrey Hepburn, Grace Kelly, and Blair Waldorf. What is it about each of those style icon that you love the most?&lt;/strong&gt; I love Audrey Hepburn’s elegance. It’s amazing, she just has this natural beauty and glamour. I love that Grace Kelly’s style focuses on simplicity making it timeless and recreatable. She always looks so pulled together. Blair Waldorf is just amazing at pulling off outfits. She combines so many elements, patterns, and colors, some outfits you know you wouldn’t have thought about combining, but somehow she pulls it off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are there any websites or online resources that you turn to for guidance with respect to blogging and maintaining your blog?&lt;/strong&gt; IFB for sure! There’s so many articles that cover a large range of topics regarding tips on blogging, marketing, ideas, etc. If there’s a question about fashion blogging you will for sure find the answer on IFB.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who takes your photos for you, and what type of camera do you use?&lt;/strong&gt; I switch back and forth between taking pictures on my own and having my best friend take it.  I use the Leica M Series camera but when I take the pictures myself (using a stand) I use my Casio TR-350&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Does social media play a big part in your blogging process? Which social media sites do you feel are crucial?&lt;/strong&gt; Social media for sure plays a large part ! It really helps in driving traffic to my blog. I mainly use Lookbook and Chictopia as well as Facebook, Bloglovin, and Instagram.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s the most rewarding component of blogging?&lt;/strong&gt; The most rewarding component is how much fun I have. It takes a lot of time and work but it’s fun to put a lot of effort into doing something you love. It’s a whole process from taking the pictures, thinking of the content, the editing, and then the satisfaction of finally publishing the post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What has blogging taught you that you did not expect to learn?&lt;/strong&gt; Blogging taught me a lot about patience. You can’t just suddenly start a blog and expect things to go well or followers to increase in a short amount of time. You have to gradually keep working at it and making improvements everyday. At first I was really frustrated when pictures didn’t turn out right, or I couldn’t make the right words for what I wanted to say or if my visitor counts were down that month!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Any advice for aspiring fashion bloggers?&lt;/strong&gt; Reach out to other bloggers and use as many resources as you can! Try to collect as many perspective as you can to figure out what direction you want to take your blog. It’s hard to start blogging when you’re not sure what you’re doing, so I find it best to gradually figure out what’s you and what you like so you can have a clear focus on working towards that goal.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2015 09:00:14 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://blogspotter.co/couture-crush/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blogspotter.co/couture-crush/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Fashion</category>
        
        <category>Interviews</category>
        
        <category>c</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Trendy Peace</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kerri Ann Moriarty&lt;/strong&gt; of &lt;strong&gt;A Trendy Peace&lt;/strong&gt; knows a thing or two about blogging. The Bostonian has learned a thing or two about dressing for cold weather (thanks to Mother Nature’s gift of copious amounts of snow), she prefers espresso over a latte, and her main source of inspiration is other bloggers. Get to know the brunette beauty today with Blogspotter.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tell us a little bit about A Trendy Peace&lt;/strong&gt; A Trendy Peace is a place where I can share two of my favorite things – shopping and styling looks. It’s been a great platform to further my extreme shopaholic tendencies. My goal is to put together looks that are a mix of high end and budget friendly pieces and it’s a fun place to explore different trends and styles that I don’t always get to wear around work and everyday life. A Trendy Peace is my creative outlet and it’s an added bonus that so many wonderful people follow along and support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When did you officially start blogging?&lt;/strong&gt; ATP kicked off officially in July 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How does living in Boston, MA influence your style?&lt;/strong&gt; It can be tricky trying to find looks that are weather appropriate during the cooler seasons, like now for example when it’s consistently less than zero degrees and there is about seven feet of snow on the ground. Every morning I wonder if it’s worth risking frostbite or a broken ankle to wear a great pair of heels. Boston is such a fun city with so many different styles, it’s fun to people watch for style inspiration. Boston’s business scene definitely shows up in my style a lot where I mix boardroom friendly pieces with casual or girly pieces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did you formally study fashion as an undergrad? If not, do you find that you’re able to incorporate what you did study into your blog?&lt;/strong&gt; I’ve never formally studied fashion; my education background is in finance and business. If you’re looking to collaborate with brands or grow a large following, running a blog is a lot like running a business so I do find myself applying some of what I’ve learned to the blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s your main source of style inspiration?&lt;/strong&gt; Other bloggers! I’ve been following some of my favorite blogs for years and whether my style shows a subtle influence or is outright duplicating a look, I am always trying to catch up all of my favorites’ new posts. Oh yeah, and Vogue helps too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How would you describe your personal style?&lt;/strong&gt; It definitely varies a lot, I think the principles to my style are to find trends and pieces that really work for my body and the philosophy of investment pieces. You’ll see I often wear oversize tops with skinnier bottoms because I love how I feel in that style – and with the addition of a gorgeous designer handbag, that budget friendly T.J. Maxx outfit takes you from looking like a million bucks – to ten million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QUICK! Latte or cappuccino?&lt;/strong&gt; Latte! Although honestly, usually it’s just an espresso, please!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QUICK! Navy or black?&lt;/strong&gt; All black everythang – it’s a classic look that can never go out of style.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you have a favorite accessory? What is it?&lt;/strong&gt; A good handbag. My Louis Vuitton speedy will probably forever be my favorite accessory because it was the first investment piece I ever bought – I bought it after college and a few months at my big girl job to celebrate officially being a grownup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are there any websites or online resources that you turn to for guidance with respect to blogging and maintaining your blog?&lt;/strong&gt; I schedule my posts once a week using Blogger, Hootsuite, and the tools available on Facebook. I work with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.tisket.com/&quot;&gt;Tisket&lt;/a&gt; to create the shoppable carousels in each of my blog posts. And I use Lightroom for editing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who takes your photos for you, and what type of camera do you use?&lt;/strong&gt; When I’m lucky, Jill from &lt;a href=&quot;http://maggiejillphotography.weebly.com/&quot;&gt;Maggie Jill Photography&lt;/a&gt; takes my photos – she was the first person to help me get the blog started. She shoots with a Nikon D610. When she’s busy being fabulous and running her own business, my wonderful manfriend takes my photos using a Nikon D3100.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Does social media play a big part in your blogging process? Which social media sites do you feel are crucial to your success?&lt;/strong&gt; Absolutely. I don’t think a soul would know about the blog if it weren’t for Instagram. I think IG is the most important for me, followed by Bloglovin and Facebook. I think it’s important to give people access to your blog on any channel, so they can follow along with you the way they want to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s the most rewarding component of blogging?&lt;/strong&gt; Being able to share something I love and am passionate about with so many wonderful, sweet, people. The amount of support in the blogging community is amazing – everyone is so supportive and only has nice things to say. Finding new bloggers gives me new sources of style inspiration and it’s wonderful to connect with ladies all over the world who have as big a shopping habit as I do!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What has blogging taught you that you did not expect to learn?&lt;/strong&gt; That it makes you feel really great to wear a fabulous outfit everyday, that there are SO many more places to shop than I thought, and that taking great selfies is SO much harder than it looks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you were to give one piece of advice to an aspiring blogger, what would it be?&lt;/strong&gt; Share the love. Don’t be afraid to tell other bloggers (or anyone for that matter) that you love their look. Getting a compliment on a look I’ve styled makes my day and it’s a great way to start connecting with other bloggers and get your blog out there!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 09:00:27 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://blogspotter.co/a-trendy-peace/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blogspotter.co/a-trendy-peace/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Fashion</category>
        
        <category>Interviews</category>
        
        <category>a</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
